A Guide to the State Treasurer's Correspondence of the Virginia Dept. of the Treasury, 1962-2022
Library of Virginia
- State Treasurer's correspondence, 1962-1999.
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1998. (Box 33)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1997. (Box 33)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1996. (Box 33)
  - Social Services, Dept. of, 1992-1997. (Box 33)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1991-1995. (Box 33)
  - NAST: Final Pension Survey Report, 1991. (Box 33)
  - News articles, 1992. (Box 33)
  - Media, 1991-1992. (Box 33)
  - JLARC - Report to the General Assembly, 1995. (Box 33)
  - Awards, 1994-1996. (Box 33)
  - State Treasury Profiles, 1989. (Box 33)
  - State Treasury Profiles, 1991. (Box 33)
  - State Treasury Profiles, 1995. (Box 33)
  - State Finance Directory, 1992. (Box 33)
  - State Treasury - Activities and functions, 1997. (Box 33)
  - Agency Procurement and Surplus Property Manual, 1998. (Box 33)
  - Local Government Investment Pool - Investment Circular, 1995. (Box 33)
  - Decentralization Pilot Projects in Higher Education, 1997. (Box 33)
  - NAST Annual Conference, 1995. (Box 33)
  - NAST LGIP Task Force, 1993-1995. (Box 33)
- State Treasurer's correspondence, 2005-2022.
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Audit (FY14), 2014. (Box 1)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Exit Conference (FY13), 2013. (Box 1)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Audit Report (FY15), 2015. (Box 1)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Audit Report (FY16), 2016. (Box 1)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Audit, 2012 May 10. (Box 1)
  - Debt capacity, 2015. (Box 1)
  - Debt Capacity Advisory Committee (DCAC) - Meeting, 2010 Sept. (Box 1)
  - Dept Capacity Advisory Committee (DCAC) - Pre-meeting, 2016 Dec 12. (Box 1)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Audit, 2017. (Box 1)
  - Virginia Port Authority (VPA) - Virginia International Gateway (VIG) Long term lease, 2016. (Box 1)
  - Republic of Gabon meeting, 2017 June 15. (Box 1)
  - China Ministry of Finances meeting, 2017. (Box 1)
  - Overview of Debt Capacity - Briefing for Secretary Layne, 2017 Dec 15. (Box 1)
  - Travel, 2019. (Box 1)
  - Travel, 2022. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file, 2022. (Box 1)
  - Travel, 2021. (Box 1)
  - Travel, 2020. (Box 1)
  - Meetings - Human Resources, undated. (Box 1)
  - Meetings - Administrative Services, 2017-2018. (Box 1)
  - Meetings - Information Systems, 2017-2018. (Box 1)
  - Meetings - Internal Review, 2017-2018. (Box 1)
  - Meetings - Debt Management, 2017-2018. (Box 1)
  - Meetings - Risk Management, 2017-2018. (Box 1)
  - Meetings - Operations, 2017-2018. (Box 1)
  - Meetings - Unclaimed Property, 2017-2018. (Box 1)
  - Audit - Certification letter to financial institutions, 2009. (Box 1)
  - Treasurer Decision Requests, 2019. (Box 1)
  - Treasurer Decision Requests, 2020. (Box 1)
  - Congressional Delegation, 2016. (Box 1)
  - Center for Retirement Initiatives, 2014. (Box 1)
  - BB and T - Chris Bradley, 2017. (Box 1)
  - Unclaimed Property - Constituent correspondence, 2018-2022. (Box 2)
  - Letters, 2019. (Box 2)
  - Constituent letters, 2012-2018. (Box 2)
  - Leters, 2015. (Box 2)
  - Leadership Team meetings, 2016-2022. (Box 2)
  - Director meetings, 2017. (Box 2)
  - Travel, 2021. (Box 2)
  - Travel, 2019. (Box 2)
  - Meetings with Secretary Layne, 2019. (Box 2)
  - Standard and Poor's - Local Government Investment Pool (LGIP), 2018. (Box 2)
  - Box contents, undated. (Box 2)
  - Credit / Interest Rates meeting, 2020 Aug 17. (Box 2)
  - Local Government Investment Pool (LGIP) - Standard and Poor's Rating Management meeting, 2019 Aug 7. (Box 2)
  - David Swynford, 2021. (Box 2)
  - Debt Management - Staff meeting, 2015-2018. (Box 2)
  - Cash Management and Investments - Staff meetings, 2021. (Box 2)
  - Human Resources - Staff meeting, 2017. (Box 2)
  - Information Systems - Staff meeting, 2018. (Box 2)
  - Internal Review - Staff meeting, 2018. (Box 2)
  - Operations - Staff meeting, 2018. (Box 2)
  - Risk Management - Staff meeting, 2018. (Box 2)
  - Information Systems Security Officer - Staff meeting, 2018. (Box 2)
  - Unclaimed Property - Staff meetings, 2017-2018. (Box 2)
  - Agency Head meeting, 2021. (Box 2)
  - Virginia Port Authority - FY20 Budget, 2020. (Box 2)
  - Virginia Port Authority - Finance and Audit, 2018 Apr 30. (Box 2)
  - Treasury Board / Virginia Port Authority MELP, 2017. (Box 2)
  - Risk Management - Constituent correspondence, 2018-2020. (Box 2)
  - P/E Investments, 2018. (Box 2)
  - Debt Management - Fidelity / Secondary Trades, 2015. (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Bill Coba - Co-Head, North America Institutional Investor Relations, 2019 Mar 21. (Box 2)
  - Treasury Logo, 2019. (Box 2)
  - Trust Accounting overtime, undated. (Box 2)
  - TUP / Cardinal Staff Recognition, 2018. (Box 2)
  - Tax Strategice Plan, 2015. (Box 2)
  - Syntec - Bill Zuk, 2017. (Box 2)
  - Higher Education - Risk Management Program, 2014. (Box 2)
  - Education 5 Paycard Secretary, 2015-2017. (Box 2)
  - Risk Managment - Dombo v. Lyons, 2018. (Box 2)
  - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 2017. (Box 2)
  - Director's Roundtable, 2010. (Box 2)
  - Securities and Exchange, 2014. (Box 2)
  - Quinton Jeffries, 2016. (Box 2)
  - Public Private Partnership Guidelines, 2014. (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Secretary Brown, undated. (Box 2)
  - Meetings, 2017. (Box 2)
  - Meeting with Lyndon Lyman, 2017 May 18. (Box 2)
  - Debt Capacity Advisory Committee (DCAC) Overview Presentations, 2017. (Box 2)
  - Delegate Landes - Concentration Banks, 2017. (Box 2)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - VCU Management Agreement, 2017. (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - William and Mary / Restructured Financial and Administration Operations Act of 2005, undated. (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - George Mason University, 2009. (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Old Dominion University, 2008-2009. (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - James Madison University, 2008. (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Virginia Military Institute, 2008. (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Radford University, 2008. (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Level II / Letters and requests, 2007. (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Level III / Letters and requests, 2007. (Box 3)
  - Higher Education Restructuring, 2007. (Box 3)
  - Decision Requests, 2021. (Box 4)
  - Decision Requests, 2022. (Box 4)
  - House Appropriations Committee Presentation, 2013 Nov. (Box 4)
  - Literary Fund Briefing to House and Senate, 2016 Dec 20. (Box 4)
  - House Finance Committee, 2015. (Box 4)
  - House Appropriations Committee presentations, 2020 Feb. (Box 4)
  - State Street presentations, 2021 June. (Box 4)
  - House Appropriations Committee - Debt Capacity presentations, undated. (Box 4)
  - Ric Brown Presentation to House and Senate, 2018 May 18. (Box 4)
  - Governor's Revenue Report Remarks to Joint Money Committee / Presentation to Secretary of Finance, 2018 Aug 17. (Box 4)
  - Actuarial Analysis of the Constitutional Officers Regional Jail (VARisk) Program, 2018 Nov. (Box 4)
  - Binational Treasury Forum, 2021 Jan 13. (Box 4)
  - Secretary's Briefing to the Money Committees, 2020 June. (Box 4)
  - Libyan Finance Ministry, 2012. (Box 4)
  - Senate Finance Committee, 2015 Oct 22. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Retirement System - Senate Finance Committee, 2013 Sept. (Box 4)
  - Subcommittee on Capital Outlay, 2013 Jan. (Box 4)
  - Presentations, 2020. (Box 4)
  - Travel, 2012. (Box 4)
  - Training, 2014. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Resource Authority - Conference, 2014 Dec. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Resource Authority - Presentation, 2012 Dec. (Box 4)
  - Decision Requests, 2021. (Box 4)
  - J.P. Morgan, 2018 June. (Box 4)
  - PFM, 2018 May 18. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Investor Conference, 2015. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Investor Conference, 2017. (Box 4)
  - Association of Governmental Accountants, 2018 Apr 19. (Box 4)
  - KAPS Demonstration, 2020 Jan. (Box 4)
  - Revenue Report - Remarks to Joint Money Committee, 2018 Aug. (Box 4)
  - Revenue Report, 2018 Oct. (Box 4)
  - Treasury Overview, 2018 Sept. (Box 4)
  - Joint Money Committee presentations, 2019 Aug. (Box 4)
  - Chronological file, 2021. (Box 4)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST) - Lexington, 2013. (Box 5)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST) - Executive Director Search, 2013-2014. (Box 5)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST) - Visit, 2011 Sept 26. (Box 5)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST) - Personnel Committee, 2011 Apr. (Box 5)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST) - Personnel Committee, 2011 June. (Box 5)
  - National Association of State Treasurers (NAST) - Interim Report, 2011. (Box 5)
  - Higher Education Restructuring, 2005-2006. (Box 6)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Chapters 933, 945 and 943, 2006. (Box 6)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Performance Measures, 206-2008. (Box 6)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Virginia Tech / Carilion Medical School, 2007. (Box 6)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Virginia Commonwealth University management agreement, 2005-2007. (Box 6)
  - Financial and Administrative management measures, 2007. (Box 6)
  - Governor's Cabinet Retreat - Briefing book, 2007 June 16. (Box 6)
  - Overview of the Base Adequacy Funding Guidelines (DPB), 2007 Oct 30. (Box 6)
  - Higher Education Restructuring, 2006. (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Debt Management Certification letters, 2006-2008. (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Miscellaneous correspondence and legislation, 2006-2008. (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Higher Education bonds, 2007. (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU) Level III, 2007 Apr. (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Goal #11 Working Group, 2006 Oct. (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Restructuring Act, 2004-2007. (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Restructuring, 2006. (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Reading material, 2006. (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Debt Management Policy, 2008. (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Level III Institutions of Higher Education / Analysis of Sole Source Orders and eVA Fees, 2006-2007. (Box 7)
  - Governor Kaine's Trade Mission to Japan, Hong Kong, and India, 2007 Apr 15-28. (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 2017-2018. (Box 8)
  - National Association of State Auditors, Comptrollers and Treasurers (NASACT), 2017. (Box 8)
  - Budget, 2016-2018, 2018-2020. (Box 8)
  - Middle River Jail Authority, 2017-2018. (Box 8)
  - Surviving and Thriving in the New Liquidity Environment, 2014-2017. (Box 8)
  - Rating Agencies, 2013-2018. (Box 8)
  - Reading material, 2018-2019. (Box 8)
  - Trip to Mexico, 2019. (Box 8)
  - Meetings with Optimal Group, 2017. (Box 8)
  - Passive investing, 2017 June 5. (Box 8)
  - VA529, 2017-2018. (Box 8)
  - India Trade Mission, 2007. (Box 8)